thehardwarehut.com 2007-12-01

# The Hardware Hut - Online and Privacy Policy

| 

**You are here:** Main Menu > Online Policies

Protecting your privacy is very important to www.thehardwarehut.com and The Hardware Hut. This document will help you to understand our policies regarding your personal information. 

**Information Collection** There are times that we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your E-mail address, telephone number and your postal address. This information is used for purposes such as correspondence, site registration, making a purchase, entering a contest or sweepstakes, registering for a new product, or participating in an online survey. If you do not wish for us to contact you, you can choose to "[opt out](mailto:remove@spokane-hardware.com)," and www.thehardwarehut.com & The Hardware Hut will respect your wishes. 

When a credit card number is supplied for a purchase, this information is used internally exclusively to process payment for your order and is not shared in any form with outside parties with the exception of any credit card validation service used by www.thehardwarehut.com & The Hardware Hut. 

Like many other commercial web sites, the www.thehardwarehut.com & The Hardware Hut web sites may utilize a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how the site is used. All "cookies" sent back to the originating server, are not provided to any outside parties under any circumstances, and never contain personal data of any form. 

**Information Use** If you provide us with your E-mail address, or have done so in the past, we may upon occasion send you E-mail offers. We may use information you have given us to, for example, provide a service, measure consumer interest in our various services, and inform you about new products and services. These offers may be based on information you provided in your initial transaction with us, in surveys, or from information that may indicate purchasing preferences and lifestyle. 

We also ask that you allow us to share your information in aggregate form for our presentations, no personally identifiable information is shared. 

**Your Acceptance of These Terms** By using this site, you signify your agreement to all the terms of the www.thehardwarehut.com & The Hardware Hut Privacy Policies. If you are not in agreement to this policy, please discontinue the use of this web site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the www.thehardwarehut.com & The Hardware Hut's web sites following the posting of changes to these terms is an acknowledgement of your acceptance of these changes. 

| 

Sat  December 01, 2007
